## Taejun Kim

CONTACT Ph.D. Candidate

School of Computing, KAIST

Email: taejun.kim@kaist.ac.kr
URL: https://taejun20.github.io

Kim Byung Ho IT Building (N1) #722 KAIST, 291 Daehak-ro, Yuseong-gu Daejeon 34141, Republic of Korea

RESEARCH INTERESTS I'm interested in devising new AR/VR interactions utilizing eye gaze movement. The integration of sensing technology into modern wearable devices has opened new possibilities of eye gaze-based interaction. Object-attachable, non-wearable eye tracking products even extend the domain into IoT applications. My research interests include eye gaze-based interaction, AR/VR interfaces, and wearable haptic interfaces.

**PUBLICATIONS** 

## **International Conference Papers**

1. Lattice Menu: A Low-Error Gaze-Based Marking Menu Utilizing Target-Assisted Gaze Gestures on a Lattice of Visual Anchors

Taejun Kim, Auejin Ham, Sunggeun Ahn, Geehyuk Lee

CHI 2022: ACM Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems

2. QuadStretch: A Forearm-wearable Multi-dimensional Skin Stretch Display for Immersive VR Haptic Feedback

Youngbo Aram Shim, Taejun Kim, Geehyuk Lee

CHI 2022 EA (Demonstration): ACM Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems

3. Heterogeneous Stroke: Using Unique Vibration Cues to Improve the Wrist-Worn Spatiotemporal Tactile Display

Taejun Kim, Youngbo Aram Shim, Geehyuk Lee

CHI 2021: ACM Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems

## **International Journal Papers**

1. WristMenu with Tactons: An Eyes- and Ears-free Menu with Tactons Describing Menu Items in the Wrist Rotation Space

Eunhye Youn, Taejun Kim, Geehyuk Lee

IJHCI 2022: International Journal of Human-Computer Interaction (Impact Factor: 3.353)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Meta Reality Labs, Toronto, Canada

Jun. 2022 – Dec. 2022

ERIENCE Ph.D. Research Intern

Bhaptics DEC. 2015 – Feb. 2016

Frontend coder

- Web interface development, service page renewal

**AWARDS** 

CHI '22 Best Demo Award, ACM Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems MAY. 2022

Demonstrating "QuadStretch: A Forearm-wearable Multi-dimensional Skin Stretch Display for Immersive VR Haptic Feedback"

Outstanding Master's Thesis Award, KAIST School of Computing

FAB. 2021

Thesis Title: "Improving Recognition Accuracy of Wrist-Worn Spatiotemporal Tactile Display using Heterogeneous Vibrotactile Stimuli"

EDUCATION

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, Korea SEP. 2020 – Present

Ph.D. Candidate in Computer Science

SEP. 2020 – Present

Advisor: Geehyuk Lee, Ph.D.

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, Korea

2020

M.S. in Computer Science

TAEJUN KIM 1 Last update: March 31, 2023

Thesis: "Improving Recognition Accuracy of Wrist-Worn Spatiotemporal Tactile Display using Heteroge-

neous Vibrotactile Stimuli" Advisor: Geehyuk Lee, Ph.D.

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Daejeon, Korea

B.S. in Computer Science

2018

INVITED TALKS **Interface Control with Eye Movement** MAR. 2023

High-Beams seminar series, University College London

**Interface Control with Eye Movement** Nov. 2022

Stanford HCI Lunch, Stanford University

**Interface Control with Eye Movement** Nov. 2022

DGP Lab, University of Toronto

ACADEMIC SERVICE Reviewer

WHC: IEEE World Haptics Conference 2023

INTERACT: IFIP International Conference on Human-Computer Interaction

ETRA: ACM Symposium on Eye Tracking Research & Application

**TEACHING Guest Lecturer** OCT. 2021

Lecture on SPSS & R practice, CS584, KAIST

**Teaching Assistant** 

CS492 Wearable User Interface, KAIST Spring 2023 CS584 Human-Computer Interaction, KAIST Fall 2021 CS550 Software Engineering, KAIST Spring 2021 CS300 Introduction to Algorithms, KAIST Fall 2020 CS204 Discrete Mathematics, KAIST Spring 2019

CS230 System Programming, KAIST Spring 2018 CS101 Introduction to Programming, KAIST Fall 2017

TAEJUN KIM Last update: March 31, 2023